Hernan David Parada Bonell

Cll 22D # 69F 73 Bogota, Colombia

hernandavidparada@gmail.com

+57 3174510295

PROFILE

General Engineer with 6 years of experience in analysis, design and development of

software projects with clients of all kinds including retail sellers, banks,

Technical Skills in construction and integration of all the layers of the developments

(Frontend, Backend and database) in technologies combination like Angular - .NET

C# - SQL Server and React - Java EE - Oracle

Personal Active participation in training new team members and constant communication

with the clients, always open to learn.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Developer

Asesoftware 2021 – 2023

Full stack developer in Angular 12, .Net core 6 and SQl Server

Taking decisions about the resources of infrastructure

Implement and solve static code analysis

Analyze and design user requirements from zero

Middle Developer

Asesoftware 2018 – 2021

Full stack developer in React, Java Enterprise Edition 7 and Oracle 11g

Leading the development team in some projects, working under the Scrum

methodology.

Planning and designing with the architect

Junior Developer

Asesoftware

Redacting user stories with the product owners

Hernan David Parada Page | 2

2017 - 2018

Develop solutions based on SOAP Architecture Work under Outsourcing model in the client's facilities

EDUCATION

Universidad de los Andes

2016

Electronic engineer

Universidad de los Andes

2016

Electrical engineer

COURSES

Udemy

2022

Docker & Kubernetes: The practical guide 2023 Edition

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-e6bcff11-807d-43c0-90e3-f46e36c6791e

SKILLS

Technical

Microsoft C# .NET

Entity Framework

REST and SOAP web Services

Angular Js, Angular 12

Azure

React

Java EE 7

Oracle 11g

Microsoft SQL server

Bootstrap

Hernan David Parada Page | 3

Personal Teamwork

Communication with clients Adapt to new technologies.

Languages English B2 certification TOEFL 2015

REFERENCES

Jhon Jairo Ibarra Technical lead

Mercado libre 3123263782

Tatiana Fuentes Analista intermedio

Asesoftware 3123856713

PERSONAL REFERENCES

Maria Alejandra Medina

Human resources

Vaxtrials 3192735109

Alejandra Caro Bonell Profesional especializado

Secretaria Distrital de Salud

3132302573

Hernan David Parada Page | 4